Guide to the R. Philip Hanes Papers, 1928-2010 RL.00503
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Ampersand: Central Files, 1976?1985
  - 1981
    - (A)
      - Ampersand Staff Memos (Box 226)
    - (B) (Box 227)
    - (C)
      - Cornell University (Box 227)
    - (D) (Box 227)
    - (F) (Box 227)
    - (G) (Box 227)
    - (H) (Box 228)
      - Hunt, Jim (Box 228)
    - (I)
      - International Communications Agency (Box 228)
    - (J) (Box 228)
    - (K) (Box 228)
    - (L) (Box 228)
    - (M) (Box 228)
    - (N)
      - NEA (Box 228)
    - (O) (Box 228)
    - (P)
      - Partners for Liveable Places (Box 228)
      - Partners for Liveable Places (Box 229)
      - Press, 3 folders (Box 229)
    - (R)
      - Reagan Task Force on the Arts (Box 229)
    - (S)
      - Salem College (Box 229)
      - Senators/Representatives (Box 229)
      - SC-ETV Network (Box 229)
    - (T)
      - Town and Country Magazine (Box 229)
      - Town and Country Magazine (Box 230)
    - (U) (Box 230)
    - (V) (Box 230)
    - (W)
      - Winston-Salem: Chamber of Commerce (Box 230)
      - Winston-Salem Development Plan: Steering Committee (Box 230)
    - (Y) (Box 230)
    - (Z) (Box 230)
  - 1982
    - (A)
      - Ampersand Memos (Box 231)
    - (B) (Box 231)
    - (C)
      - Calendars (Box 231)
    - (D) (Box 231)
    - (E) (Box 231)
    - (F) (Box 231)
    - (G) (Box 231)
    - (H)
      - Hunt, Jim (Box 231)
    - (I) (Box 231)
    - (J) (Box 231)
    - (K) (Box 232)
    - (L) (Box 232)
    - (M)
      - Mark, Charles (Box 232)
    - (N)
      - NCSA (Box 232)
      - NEA (Box 232)
    - (O) (Box 232)
    - (P)
      - Press, 2 folders (Box 233)
    - (R)
      - Reagan (Box 233)
      - Roanoak (Box 233)
    - (S)
      - Senators and Representatives (Box 233)
      - SC-ETV Network (Box 233)
    - (T) (Box 233)
    - (U) (Box 233)
    - (W)
      - Winston-Salem: Chamber of Commerce (Box 233)
      - Winston-Salem: Contracts (Box 233)
      - Winston-Salem: Development Plan (Box 233)
      - Winston-Salem: R. J. Reynolds Industries (Box 233)
      - Winston-Salem: Radisson Plaza Hotel (Box 233)
    - (Y) (Box 233)
  - 1983
    - (A)
      - American Academy in Rome (Box 233)
      - American School of Classical Studies in Athens (Box 233)
      - Ampersand Memos (Box 233)
    - (B)
      - British Arts (Box 234)
    - (C)
      - Calendars (Box 234)
    - (D)
      - Dennis Wayne's Dancers (Box 234)
    - (E) (Box 234)
    - (F) (Box 234)
    - (G) (Box 234)
    - (H)
      - International Communication Agency (Box 234)
    - (J) (Box 234)
    - (K) (Box 234)
    - (L) (Box 234)
    - (M)
      - Mark, Charles (Box 234)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 234)
    - (N)
      - North Carolina Dance Theater (Box 234)
      - NCSA: General (Box 234)
      - NCSA: Report and Proposal (Box 234)
      - NCSA: Trip Notes (Box 234)
      - NEA (Box 234)
    - (P) (Box 234)
    - (R)
      - Redford, Robert (Box 234)
    - (S) (Box 235)
      - San Francisco Art Institute Virginia Museum (Box 235)
      - Senators and Representatives (Box 235)
      - SC-ETV Network (Box 235)
    - (T) (Box 235)
    - (W)
      - Winston-Salem: Chamber of Commerce (Box 235)
      - Winston-Salem: Development Plan--Steering Committee (Box 235)
      - Winston-Salem: R. J. Reynolds Industries (Box 235)
  - 1984
    - (A)
      - Anderson Ranch (Box 235)
    - (B)
      - Berea College (Box 235)
      - British Arts (Box 235)
    - (C)
      - Council on Foundations Meeting 9/30-10/3 (Box 235)
    - (D)
      - Dennis Wayne's Dancers (Box 235)
    - (E) (Box 235)
    - (F) (Box 235)
    - (G) (Box 235)
    - (H)
      - Hunt, Jim (Box 235)
    - (J) (Box 235)
    - (K)
      - Kessler, Jack (Box 235)
    - (L) (Box 236)
      - Lissauer, Robert (Box 236)
      - Lissauer, Robert: Flim-Flam, 2 folders (Box 236)
    - (M)
      - Movement Theatre International: International Mime and Clown Festival (Box 236)
    - (N)
      - NCDT (Box 236)
      - NCSA: Board of Visitors (Box 236)
      - NCSA: Other (Box 236)
      - N.C. Visitors Center (Box 236)
    - (P)
      - Pacific Northwest Ballet--Seattle, Washington (Box 236)
    - (R) (Box 236)
    - (S)
      - Spruce Street Association, Ltd. (Box 237)
    - (T) (Box 237)
    - (V) (Box 237)
    - (W)
      - Winston-Salem: Chamber of Commerce (Box 237)
      - Winston-Salem Development Plan: Steering Committee, 2 folders (Box 237)
  - 1985
    - American Craft Council (Box 237)
    - British Arts (Box 237)
    - Dennis Wayne's Dancers (Box 237)
    - Joffrey Campaign (Box 237)
    - Leakey Foundation (Box 237)
    - N. C. Arts Council (Box 237)
    - Roanoke (Box 237)
- Ampersand Files: Company Records, 1976?1985 and undated
  Chiefly Ampersand records relating to clients, proposals, and financial records. Also included are telephone logs and a photocopied list of names and street addresses. Included are correspondence and memoranda, casebook outlines, contracts and agreements, minutes of board of director meetings, activity reports, client statements, proposals, feasibility studies, and workplans. The financial records include budgets, income and operating expenses statements, balance sheets, productivity reports, capital expenditures, and sales forecasts. The telephone logs provide the date, time, person, telephone number, city and state, and brief information regarding the purpose and instructions. This section is organized alphabetically by name of item. The clients and proposals are usually organized alphabetically by client name in groupings of years.
  - Addresses, undated (Box 238)
  - Advisory Board and Board of Directors, 1976-1978 (Box 238)
  - Clients and Proposals:
    - A-R, 1976-1985, 5 folders (Box 238)
  - Clients and Proposals: (Box 239)
    - SECCA-Z, 1976-1985, 3 folders (Box 239)
    - Back-dated Clients, 1976-1982, 3 folders (Box 239)
  - Clients and Proposals: (Box 240)
    - 1982-1985, 8 folders (Box 240)
  - Clients and Proposals: (Box 241)
    - Agreements, 1978-1985 (Box 241)
    - Analysis of Ampersand, 1977-1985, 3 folders (Box 241)
  - Financial Papers: (Box 242)
    - Income and Expenses 1976-1979, 5 folders (Box 242)
    - Budget, 1979 (Box 242)
    - Financial Statements, 1979, 2 folders (Box 242)
  - Financial Papers: (Box 243)
    - Actual Budget, 1980 (Box 243)
    - 1981, 2 folders (Box 243)
    - 1982, 2 folders (Box 243)
  - Financial Papers: (Box 244)
    - 1983-1986, 5 folders (Box 244)
  - Telephone Logs, 1979-1983, 5 folders (Box 245)
- Personal and Boards Series, 1949?1986, undated
  Chiefly letters, memoranda, and clippings. Focuses on Hanes's involvement on the boards of various organizations, pertaining to the arts as well as to conservation of natural resources. Other folders relate to his interest in outdoor recreation. Arranged alphabetically by topic, organization, or personal name.
  - Alliance for Arts Education Committee 1975-1978, March 21, 3 folders (Box 246)
  - Alliance for Arts Education Committee 1978 March-1979 October and undated, 2 folders (Box 247)
  - American Ballet Theatre, 1975 (Box 247)
  - American National Theatre Fund, 1976 (Box 247)
  - American Land Trust: Correspondence, 1976 (Box 247)
  - American Land Trust: Information, 1976 (Box 247)
  - American Land Trust: Nathan P. Reed (Box 247)
  - Appalachian Greenway, 1974 and 1980 (Box 247)
  - Appalachian Greenway: AHA Board Possibilities, 1975 (Box 247)
  - Appalachian Greenway: Bicentennial Administration, 1974 (Box 247)
  - Appalachian Greenway: Correspondence, 1972-1976 and undated, 2 folders (Box 247)
  - Appalachian Greenway: Correspondence, 1975-1976, 2 folders (Box 248)
  - Appalachian Greenway: Facts, 1972-1975 (Box 248)
  - Appalachian Greenway: History, 1974 (Box 248)
  - Appalachian Greenway: Maps/Information undated (Box 248)
  - Appalachian Greenway: Meetings/Contacts, 1974-1975 (Box 248)
  - Appalachian Greenway: Meeting, Washington, DC, 1975 (Box 248)
  - Appalachian Greenway: Testimonials, 1974 (Box 248)
  - Appalachian Trail Conference: Correspondence, 1976 (Box 248)
  - Appalachian Trail Conference: Information, 1975-1976 (Box 248)
  - Art, 1973-1978 (Box 248)
  - Art, 1979-1980 (Box 249)
  - Art: Art Economist Board, 1981-1982 (Box 249)
  - Art: Correspondence, 1971-1975, 2 folders (Box 249)
  - Art: Correspondence, 1977, 2 folders (Box 250)
  - Art: Hirshhorn, Joe, 1976 (Box 250)
  - Art: Hulmer, Eric, 1976 (Box 250)
  - Art: Kluge, John, 1975-1977 (Box 251)
  - Art: White House Festival of the Arts (Box 251)
  - Art: Winston-Salem--General (Box 251)
  - Arts Council: Winston-Salem--Civil Ballet vs IRS, 1974 (Box 251)
  - Arts Council: Winston-Salem--Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 251)
  - Arts Council: Winston-Salem--Director's Interview, 1964-1966, 2 folders (Box 251)
  - Arts Council: Winston-Salem--Interviews, 1971 (Box 252)
  - Arts Council: Winston-Salem--Study Arts: Culture, 1972-1974 (Box 252)
  - Arts, Incorporated, 1980-1984 (Box 252)
  - Arts, Incorporated: Miami, Florida, 1980-1981 June (Box 252)
  - Arts, Incorporated: Miami, Florida, 1981-June 1982 (Box 253)
  - Arts International, 1981-1984 (Box 253)
  - Arts International: Straight, Michael, 1981-1982 (Box 253)
  - Arts Resources Corporation, 1981-1982 (Box 253)
  - Associated Councils of the Arts, 1974-1976 (Box 253)
  - Awards, 1971-1983 (Box 253)
  - Awards: North Carolina Public Service Award, 1976 (Box 253)
  - Bank, 1978-1982, 2 folders (Box 254)
  - Biographical Information (Box 254)
  - Black Mountain College, 1973-1974 (Box 254)
  - Back Mountain Project, 1977 (Box 254)
  - Business Committee for the Arts, 1971-1983, 3 folders (Box 255)
  - Business Committee for the Arts, 1984 (Box 256)
  - Business Committee for the Arts: Hanes Dye and Finishing Company, 1981 (Box 256)
  - Calendar, 1982 (Box 256)
  - Cane River, 1977-1984, 3 folders (Box 256)
  - Cane River: Correspondence, 1976 (Box 256)
  - Cane River Property, 1979-1982 (Box 256)
  - Cane River: Tom Wilson, 1977 (Box 256)
  - Cane River: Tom Wilson Property, 1971-1975 (Box 256)
  - Cane River Conservancy, Inc.: Correspondence, 1968-1975 (Box 257)
  - Cane River Conservancy, Inc: Correspondence--Bagwell, 1968-1981 (Box 257)
  - Cane River Conservancy, Inc.: Information (Box 257)
  - Cane River Conservancy, Inc.: Maps, 1971 (Box 257)
  - Cane River Conservancy, Inc.: Tanglewood, 1973-1974 (Box 257)
  - Cane River Conservancy, Inc.: Correspondence--Wilson, 1970-1974 (Box 257)
  - Cane River/Wilson Property: Information, Correspondence/Options, 1970-1974 (Box 257)
  - Century Association, 1977-1984 (Box 257)
  - Century Association: Suderburg, Robert, 1978-1979 (Box 257)
  - Chief Executives Forum, 1976 (Box 257)
  - Clippings, 1961-1984 (Box 257)
  - Correspondence: Hanes, R. P., 1949-1974 August, 6 folders (Box 258)
  - Correspondence: Hanes, R. P., 1974 September-1976 September, 6 folders (Box 259)
  - Correspondence: Hanes, R. P., 1976 October-1979 August, 6 folders (Box 260)
  - Correspondence: Hanes, R. P., 1979 October-1982, 6 folders (Box 261)
  - Correspondence, 1983 January-1984 May, 6 folders (Box 262)
  - Correspondence, 1984 June-1984 December and undated, 4 folders (Box 263)
  - Creative Problem Solving Institute, 1977-1979, 2 folders (Box 263)
  - Creative Problem Solving Institute: Correspondence, 1972-1976 (Box 263)
  - Creative Problem Solving Institute: Fund Raising, 1973 and 1976, 2 folders (Box 264)
  - Currituck (Box 264)
  - Currituck, 1979-1981 (Box 264)
  - Currituck and Pine Island (Box 264)
  - Currituck County Project, 1972-1973 (Box 264)
  - Currituck Shooting Club: General, 1976-1978 (Box 264)
  - Currituck Shooting Club, 1981-1982, 2 folders (Box 264)
  - Currituck Shooting Club, 1983-1984 (Box 265)
  - Currituck Shooting Club: Correspondence, 1961-1976 (Box 265)
  - Currituck Shooting Club: Federal Government (Box 265)
  - Currituck Shooting Club: History (Box 265)
  - Currituck Shooting Club Schedule, 1978 (Box 265)
  - Davenport, Tom, 1977-1981 (Box 265)
  - Doctorate, 9-22-81 (Box 265)
  - Donor's Forum, 1980-1983 (Box 265)
  - Donor's Forum: Winston-Salem, 1977-1979 (Box 265)
  - Ducks, 1978-1984 (Box 265)
  - Ecology, 1974-1977 (Box 265)
  - Ecology: Articles and Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 265)
  - Ecology: Coastal Zone Management, 1973-1974 (Box 265)
  - Ecology: Correspondence, 1976 (Box 265)
  - Ecology: Easements, 1957-1974 (Box 266)
  - Ecology: "Environmental Bulletin," 1973-1974 (Box 266)
  - Ecology: Finances, 1971-1976 (Box 266)
  - Ecology: General, 1973-1974 (Box 266)
  - Ecology: New River, 1974-1976 and undated, 2 folders (Box 266)
  - Ecology: Slickrock/Kilmer, 1973 (Box 266)
  - The Enterprise Foundation, 1982-1983 (Box 266)
  - The Enterprise Foundation: Rouse Co., 1981 (Box 266)
  - Federal Reserve Board of Richmond, 1977-1978 (Box 266)
  - Federal Reserve Board of Washington, DC, 1979-1980 (Box 266)
  - First Stevens Limited Partnership, 1982 (Box 267)
  - Forsyth Co. Economic Development Corp., 1968-1974 (Box 267)
  - The Foxfire Company - A Limited Partnership, 1982 (Box 267)
  - Gingrich Award (Box 267)
  - Governor's Business Council on the Arts and Humanities, 1980 and undated, 2 folders (Box 267)
  - Governor's Business Council on the Arts and Humanities, 1981-1984 and undated, 3 folders (Box 268)
  - Governor's Business Council on the Arts and Humanities: Wilson, 1980 and undated, 2 folders (Box 268)
  - Great Smoky Mountains National Park, 1965-1966 (Box 268)
  - Hall of Justice, 1977 (Box 268)
  - Hanes Dye and Finishing Co., 1978 (Box 268)
  - Hanes Dye and Finishing Co., 1979-1980, 3 folders (Box 269)
  - Hanes Dye and Finishing Co., 1981-1984, 3 folders (Box 270)
  - Hanes Dye and Finishing Co.: Art Object, 1975 (Box 270)
  - Hanes Dye and Finishing Co.: Caisson Corp., 1970 (Box 270)
  - Hanes Dye and Finishing Co.: Correspondence, 1971-1972, 3 folders (Box 270)
  - Hanes Dye and Finishing Co: Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 271)
  - Hanes Dye and Finishing Co.: Donations, 1982-1983 (Box 271)
  - Hanes Dye and Finishing Co.: Employees Inactive (Box 271)
  - Hanes Dye and Finishing Co.: Europe, 1970 (Box 271)
  - Hanes Dye and Finishing Co.: European Plants--Correspondence, 1970 (Box 271)
  - Hanes Dye and Finishing Co.: Pledges/Donations, 1975-1981, 2 folders (Box 271)
  - Hanes Dye and Finishing Co.: Nippon Cloth, 1973 (Box 271)
  - Hanes Dye and Finishing Co.: Pollution, 1974 (Box 272)
  - Hanes Dye and Finishing Co.: Public Relations, 1975 (Box 272)
  - Hanes Dye and Finishing Co.: Sales Office, 1975 (Box 272)
  - Hanes Dye and Finishing Co.: Spartan Mills, 1972 (Box 272)
  - Hanes Dye and Finishing Co.: The Unions, 1973 (Box 272)
  - Heritage Trust, N.C., 1975-1976 (Box 272)
  - Hides and Straps, 1977 (Box 272)
  - Hubert H. Humphrey Institute, 1985 (Box 272)
  - Hump Mountain, 1981 (Box 272)
  - Izaak Walton League of America, 1976-1979, 2 folders (Box 273)
  - Izaak Walton League of America: Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 273)
  - Izaak Walton League of America: Fund Raising, 1976 (Box 273)
  - Izaak Walton League of America: Meetings, 1976 (Box 273)
  - The Jargon Society, Inc., 1973-1979, 5 folders (Box 273)
  - The Jargon Society, Inc., 1980, 1983-1984, 2 folders (Box 274)
  - The Jargon Society: Archives (Box 274)
  - The Jargon Society: Articles-Information (Box 274)
  - The Jargon Society: Correspondence, 1976 (Box 274)
  - The Jargon Society: Williams, Jonathan, 1969-1972, 1976-1980, 5 folders (Box 274)
  - The Jargon Society: Williams, Jonathan, 1981-1982 (Box 275)
  - The Jargon Society: Williams, Jonathan: Correspondence, 1972-1975, 2 folders (Box 275)
  - The John Wesley and Anna Hodgin Hanes Foundation (Box 276)
  - The John Wesley and Anna Hodgin Hanes Foundation, 1978-1984 (Box 276)
  - Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts (Box 276)
  - Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts, 1977-1980 (Box 276)
  - Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts: Auditor's Report, 1975 (Box 276)
  - Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts: Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 276)
  - Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts: Development Program, 1972 (Box 276)
  - Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts: Friends, 1975-1976 (Box 276)
  - Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts: Golden Circle, 1975-1976 (Box 276)
  - Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts: Information, 1976 (Box 276)
  - Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts: Stevens, Roger, 1975-1976 (Box 276)
  - Knox, Eddie, 1984 (Box 277)
  - Lowry, W. McNeil: Foundation for Humanities to the Arts, 1973-1974 (Box 277)
  - Maloof, Sam, 1979-1980 (Box 277)
  - Metcalf and Blankenship Options, 1978 (Box 277)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 277)
  - Morrison Award for the Arts, 1977 (Box 277)
  - Mount Rogers, Virginia, 1978-1979 (Box 277)
  - The Museum of Modern Art: International Council, 1976-1984, 3 folders (Box 278)
  - National Audubon Society, 1972-1973, 4 folders (Box 278)
  - National Audubon Society: Correspondence, 1973-1979, 4 folders (Box 279)
  - National Audubon Society: Ducks, 1975 March-November, 2 folders (Box 279)
  - National Audubon Society: Ducks, 1975, Dec.-1976 (Box 280)
  - National Audubon Society: Fund Raising--Development, 1975 (Box 280)
  - National Audubon Society: Fund Raising--Promoting Life Memberships,, 1973-1974 (Box 280)
  - National Audubon Society: Information (Box 280)
  - National Audubon Society: Meetings, 1976 (Box 281)
  - National Audubon Society: Memberships and Computer Readouts, undated (Box 281)
  - National Audubon Society: Nomination Commission, 1975-1976 (Box 281)
  - National Audubon Society: N.C. Wildlife Federation, 1973 (Box 281)
  - National Audubon Society: Pollution, 1975 (Box 281)
  - National Audubon Society: Proposed Budgets, 1974-1977, 2 folders (Box 281)
  - National Collection of Fine Arts Commission, 1976-1980 (Box 281)
  - National Council for Arts and Education, 1976-1980 (Box 281)
  - National Endowment for the Arts: Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 281)
  - National Endowment for the Arts: Correspondence, 1974-1979 (Box 282)
  - National Endowment for the Arts: Music Panel, 1974, Dec. 4-7 (Box 282)
  - National Endowment for the Arts: Stevens, Roger, 1967-1976 and undated, 3 folders (Box 282)
  - National Governor's Association, 1982 (Box 282)
  - National Museum of American Art Commission, 1980-1984, 2 folders (Box 282)
  - National Park Service: Management Policies, 1975 (Box 282)
  - National Recreation and Park Association, 1976 (Box 282)
  - The Nature Conservancy, 1970-1984 and undated, 7 folders (Box 283)
  - The Nature Conservancy, undated--Index (Box 284)
  - The Nature Convervancy: Board of Governors Meeting, 1976 Sept. 11-1979 Sept. 28, 2 folders (Box 284)
  - The Nature Conservancy: North Carolina Nature Conservancy, 1976 (Box 284)
  - Nature Science Center, 1974-1975 (Box 284)
  - Navy Reports, 1949-1953 (Box 284)
  - New River, 2 folders (Box 284)
  - New River: 77 1/2 Acres, 1963-1980 (Box 284)
  - N.C. Governor's Business Council, 1983 (Box 285)
  - NCSA: "Are the Bozarts Blooming?, 1971 (Box 285)
  - North Carolina School of the Arts (NCSA), 1965-1981 and undated (Box 285)
  - NCSA: Correspondence, 1967-1981 and undated, 2 folders (Box 285)
  - NCSA: Dance, 1970 (Box 285)
  - NCSA: deMille, Agnes, 1970-1974 (Box 285)
  - NCSA: Drama Interviews, 1975 (Box 285)
  - NCSA: Goal for 1968-1970 (Box 285)
  - NCSA: Hall, Roger, 1970 (Box 285)
  - NCSA: 1. History of Giving 2. Prospective Contributors (Box 285)
  - NCSA: Legislative Session--Budget, 1974 (Box 286)
  - NCSA: Search Committee, 1973-1976 and undated, 2 folders (Box 286)
  - NCSA: Suderburg, Robert--Installation, 1974 (Box 286)
  - NCSA: Tenure, 1974 (Box 286)
  - NCSA: Theatre Building, 1975 (Box 286)
  - Orders, 1975 (Box 286)
  - Parks: National and State, 1967-1975 and undated (Box 286)
  - Parks: Smokies, 1971-1975 (Box 286)
  - Pauline Kroner Dance Board, 1981 (Box 286)
  - Penland School of Crafts, 1968-1978 (Box 286)
  - Pennsylvania Academy of the Arts, 1977 (Box 286)
  - Piedmont Craftsmen, 1976 (Box 286)
  - Pine Island Property (Box 286)
  - Pine Island and Roan (Box 287)
  - Political Candidates: Correspondence, 1972 (Box 287)
  - Politics: North Carolina, 1976 (Box 287)
  - Politics: North Carolina--General, 1974-1975 (Box 287)
  - Politics: Patton/Woodhouse Affair (Box 287)
  - Politics: Rohrer, Grace, 1972-1974 (Box 287)
  - Politics: Washington, 1964-1976 (Box 287)
  - President's Committee on the Arts and Humanities, 1982 (Box 287)
  - Projects: The Frame Shop and Chameleon Galleries, 1976 (Box 287)
  - Projects: Hall of Justice, 1976 (Box 287)
  - Projects: Hides and Straps, 1976 (Box 287)
  - Projects: Shaw's Tire Service, 1970-1979 and undated (Box 287)
  - Recreation Future of the South: Camp Yonahnoka (Box 287)
  - Roan Mountain, 1977-1979, 2 folders (Box 287)
  - Roan Mountain: Donations--Checks Sent (Box 287)
  - Roan Mountain: Maps, Information, 1977 (Box 287)
  - Roaring Gap, 1975 (Box 287)
  - Royall, Don Ray: Property (Box 287)
  - Salzburg Seminar in American Studies, 1975-1984 and undated, 4 folders (Box 288)
  - Scrapbook, 1977-1981 and undated (Box 288)
  - Scrapbook: Ampersand's Christmas Book to Philip Hanes, 1978 (Box 288)
  - Scrapbook: Christmas Present from Ampersand Staff, 1977 (Box 288)
  - Social Register Letters, 1977 (Box 288)
  - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art (SECCA) October 18-19, 1976 (Box 288)
  - SECCA: Articles/Endorsement, 1974-1980 (Box 288)
  - SECCA: Correspondence and Fund Raising, 1974-1975 (Box 289)
  - SECCA: Correspondence--General, 1972-1974 (Box 289)
  - SECCA: Enclosures, 1976 (Box 289)
  - SECCA: Information, 1972 (Box 289)
  - SECCA: Master Copy, 1975 and undated (Box 289)
  - SECCA: Stationery, Pledge Cards, and undated (Box 289)
  - Southern Federation of State Arts Agencies: Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 289)
  - Southern Growth Policies Board, 1971 (Box 289)
  - Speech File, 1977 (Box 289)
  - Spoleto Festival USA, Inc., 1979-1981 Dec., 3 folders (Box 289)
  - Spoleto Festival USA, Inc., 1982-1984 and undated, 3 folders (Box 290)
  - Spoleto Festival USA, Inc.: Annual Report, 1981 (Box 290)
  - Spoleto Festival USA, Inc.: Charleston, Nov. 17, 1981 (Box 290)
  - Spoleto Festival USA, Inc.: Charleston--Agendas, May 29, 1980 (Box 290)
  - Stevens Center, 1981 Jan-1982 July, 3 folders (Box 290)
  - Stevens Center, 1982 Aug-1983 April, 6 folders (Box 291)
  - Stevens Center: Fund Raising, 1979 (Box 291)
  - Stevens Center: Invittees--Nationally, 1979-1980 (Box 292)
  - Stevens Center: List, 1982-1983 (Box 292)
  - Stevens Center: Opening, 1981-1982 (Box 292)
  - Stevens Center: Redevelopment, 1978-1980 (Box 292)
  - Stone Mountain, 1977-1982, 3 folders (Box 292)
  - Trips, 1978-1979 (Box 292)
  - Trips: Alliance for Arts, 1976 (Box 293)
  - Trips: American Craftsmen's Council, 1976-1977 (Box 293)
  - Trips: Associated Councils of the Arts, 1977 (April-May) (Box 293)
  - Trips: Baltimore, 1984-1985 (Box 293)
  - Trips: Business Committee for the Arts, Inc.: June 13 and 14 Minneapolis BCA, 1979 (Box 293)
  - Trips: Cane River, 1976-1978 (Box 293)
  - Trips: Chattanooga, Tennessee, 1983-1984 (Box 293)
  - Trips: Duke University, 1977 (Box 293)
  - Trips: England, 1982 (Box 293)
  - Trips: Hewlett Foundation, 1978-1979 (Box 293)
  - Trips: Hirshhorn Award--New York, 1979 (Box 293)
  - Trips: The Izaak Walton League of America, 1977 (Box 293)
  - Trips: JDR III Meeting, May 8-11, 1978 (Box 294)
  - Trips: Jackson, Mississippi, 1984-1986 (Box 294)
  - Trips: Jacksonville, Florida, January 25-26, 1983 (Box 294)
  - Trips: Jamestown, New York, 1983 (Box 294)
  - Trips: Jordan, 1979 February 15-1979 March 4 (Box 294)
  - Trips: Kennedy Center, 1977 (Box 294)
  - Trips: Kennedy Center Gala, 1979 December 1 and 2 (Box 294)
  - Trips: London, 1978 June 2-27 (Box 294)
  - Trips: Mexico, 1975-1976 (Box 294)
  - Trips: National Audubon Society--New York City, 1977 December 5 and 10 (Box 294)